Guide to the Peter H.L. and Edith Chang Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Chiang, Mei-ling Soong
    - Chiang, Mei-ling Soong To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (4 autograph cards signed ) (Box 01, Folder 14.02)
  - Chiang, Ching-kuo
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chiang Ching-kuo [also as Jiang Jing-guo], [Taipei] 14/6/M46 [1957], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 01.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chiang Ching-kuo, [Taipei] 8/5/1960, (1 page, typed letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 01.01)
      [Note: See Mei-ling Soong Chiang [Box 1, Folder 11.5]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chiang Ching-kuo, [Taipei]7/10/M63 [1974], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 01.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chiang Ching-kuo, [Taipei] 19/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 01.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chiang Ching-kuo, [Taipei] 27/9/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 01.01)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Chiang Ching-kuo, [Taipei] 26/5/1961, (1/2 page, typed letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 01.02)
      [ Note: See Mei-ling Soong Chiang [Box 1, Folder 11.5]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mr.. and Mrs.. Chiang Ching-kuo, [n.p.] 8/5/1960, (1/2 page, typed letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 01.02)
      [Note: See Meil-ling Soong Chiang [Box 1, Folder 11.5]]
    - [Chiang, Ching-kuo and Faina Chiang] To [H. L. and Edith Chao Chang], [Taipei] 15/5/1961, (1 receipt ) (Box 02, Folder 01.03)
    - [Chiang, Ching-kuo and Faina Chiang] [H. L. and Edith Chao Chang], [Taipei] 5/3/1969, (1 receipt ) (Box 02, Folder 01.03)
    - [Chiang, Ching-kuo and Faina Chiang] [H. L. and Edith Chao Chang], [Taipei] 14/5/1969, (1 receipt ) (Box 02, Folder 01.03)
    - Chiang, Ching-kuo and Faina Chiang To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (2 autograph cards signed ) (Box 02, Folder 01.04)
    - Edith Chao Chang To Mr.. and Mrs.. Chiang Ching-kuo, [Taipei] 22/5/1964, (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 01.02)
    - Chiang, Ching-kuo and Faina Chiang To Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (4 autograph cards signed) (Box 02, Folder 01.04)
  - Chiang, Faina [Mrs.. Chiang Ching-kuo]
    - Chiang, Faina [Mrs.. Chiang Ching-kuo] To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1 card ) (Box 02, Folder 01.04)
    - Chiang, Faina To Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] 18/5/1966, (1 typed card signed ) (Box 02, Folder 01.04)
    - Chiang, Faina To ? [Taipei] [n.d.], (2 autograph cards signed ) (Box 02, Folder 01.04)
  - Chiang, Hsiao-wen
    - Chiang, Hsiao-wen [also as Alan Chiang, Jiang Xiao-wen] To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.01)
    - Chiang, Hsiao-wen and Nancy H. W. Chiang To Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (2 autograph cards signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.01)
      [Note: See Chiang Ching-kuo [Box 2, Folder 1.4]]
  - Chiang, Nancy H. W. [Mrs.. Chiang Hsiao-wen]
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To Edith Chao Chang, Taipei 25/7/1989, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.01)
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To Peter and Edith Chiang, Taipei [n.d.]/[n.m.]/1990, (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.01)
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To Peter and Edith Chiang, Taipei 16/8/M80 [1991], (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.01)
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To Edith Chao Chang, Taipei 9/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.02)
    - Chang, Edith Chao To Nancy H. W. Chiang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1/2 page, typed letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 02.02)
      [Note: See Chiang Ching-kuo [Box 2, Folder 1.2]]
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.02)
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.02)
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.02)
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.02)
    - Chiang, Nancy H. W. To Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 02, Folder 02.02)
  - Chiang, You mei
    - Chiang, You mei [also as Jiang You mei] To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [Taipei] 3/1/1991, (1 autograph card, with clipping ) (Box 02, Folder 02.03)
  - Chiang, Hsiao-wu
    - Chiang, Hsiao-wu [also as Jiang Xiao-wu] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 calling card ) (Box 02, Folder 02.03)
  - K’ung, H. H.
    - K’ung, H.H. [also as Kong Xiang-xi] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chungking] 27/7/[1943], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 03.01)
    - K’ung, H.H. To Peter H. L. Chang, New York 19/11/1952, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 03.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To H.H. K’ung, [Taipei] 5/5/M42 [1953], (3 page, autograph letter signed [carbon] ) (Box 02, Folder 03.02)
    - K’ung, H. H. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.]7/1/[n.y.], (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 03.06)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, pages7-10 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - K’ung, H. H. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 6/2//[n.y.], (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 03.06)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, pages 11-13 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - K’ung, H. H. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chungking] 16/2/[n.y.], (3 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 03.03)
    - K’ung, H. H. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chungking] 2/4/[n.y.], (3 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 03.04)
    - K’ung, H. H. To Peter H. L. Chang, [USA] 8/5/[n.y.] (Box 02, Folder 03.05)
      [2 page ms .l.s.]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To H.H. K’ung, [Taiwan] 17/5/[n.y.], (2 leaf. autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 03.05)
  - K’ung, L. K.
    - K’ung, L. K. [also as Kong Ling-kan] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 2/10/ 1978, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 04.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To L. K. K’ung, [n.p.] 28/10/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 04.01)
    - K’ung, L. K. To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 calling card ) (Box 02, Folder 04.01)
    - K’ung, L. K. To Edith Chao Chang, [n.p.] 3/1/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 04.01)
  - K’ung, L. Yi
    - K’ung, L. Yi [also as Kong Ling-yi] To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, New York 20/12/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 04.02)
  - Soong, T. A.
    - Soong, T. A. [also as Song Zi-an] To Peter H. L. Chang, San Francisco 9/12/1954, (1page, typed letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 05.01)
    - Soong, T. A. To Peter H. L. Chang, San Francisco 25/5/1955, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 05.02)
    - Soong, T. A. To Hollington K. Tong, [n.p.] 22/11/1960, (1 page, typed letter (copy) ) (Box 02, Folder 05.03)
    - Soong, T. A. To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, San Francisco [n.d.], (1 typed invitation and RSVP card ) (Box 02, Folder 05.04)
  - Soong, T.V.
    - Soong, T.V. [also as Song Zi-wen] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Nanking] 2/1/[1937], (1 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 02, Folder 06.01)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Shanghai] 31/7/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 06.02)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Shanghai] 22/9/[1937], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 06.03)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, Hankou 11/6/1938, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 06.04)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, Hong Kong 24/2/1939, (4 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 06.05)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, Hong Kong 10/3//1939, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 07.01)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, Chungking 25/9/1939, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 07.02)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 11/6/1940, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 07.03)
      [ ]
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chungking] 1/12/M31[1942], (7 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 07.04)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 1/3/1944, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 07.05)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 14/9/M46 [1957], (1 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 07.06)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 28/1/[n.y.], (1 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 08.01)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.]7/2/[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 08.02)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chungking] 21/2/ [n.y.], (3 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 08.03)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [New York] 24/2/[n.y.], (1 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 08.04)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 2/3/[n.y.], (4 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 08.05)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Hankou] 4/4/[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 09.01)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 5/4/[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 09.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To T.V.Soong, [n.p.] 19/4/[n.y.], (5 leaf, autograph letter (draft), and calling card ) (Box 02, Folder 09.03)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 5/5/[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 02, Folder 09.04)
      [Note: See San Yu Tang [Box 6. Folder 13.2]]]
    - Soong, T. V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 5/5 [n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 10.02)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 18/6/[n.y.], (1 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 09.05)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chungking] 12/7/[n.y.], (4 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 10.01)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chungking] 3/8/[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 10.02)
    - Soong, T.V. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Chungking] 10/10[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 02, Folder 10.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To T. V. Soong, [n.p., n.d.], (5 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 10.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To T. V. Soong, [n.p., n.d.], (2 leaf. autograph letter draft) (Box 02, Folder 10.05)
  - Bai, Chong-xi
    - Bai, Chong-xi [also as Pai Ch’ung-his] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 27/9/[ny], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 01)
  - Baldwin, Laura
    - Baldwin, Laura To H. L. and Edith Chao Chang, Baltimore,MD 17/2/1957, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.01)
  - Bao, Wen-yue
    - Bao, Wen-yue To Peter H. L. Chang, [Xi An] 10/1/[1937], (5 page, manuscript letter signed. ) (Box 03, Folder 02.01)
      [Note: See Sun, Wei-ru [Box 4]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Bao Wen-yue, [n.p.] 12/10/[n.y.], (2 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 02.02)
  - Barrow, Luci Mayer
    - Barrow, Luci Mayer To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 26/3/1930 (Box 06, Folder 06.02)
      [4 page t.d. and calling card]
  - Baxter, C. R.
    - Baxter, C. R. To Peter H. L. Chang, N. Hollywood,CA 14/7/1961, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.03)
  - Bu, Shao-fu
    - Bu, Shao-fu [also as Pu Shao-fu] To Peter H. L. Chang, [HK] 11/4/1992, (1page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 03.01)
      [Note: See Media [Box 6, Folder 11.1]]
    - Bu, Shao-fu To Peter H. L. Chang, [HK] 6/4/1992, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 03.02)
    - Bu Shao-fu To Peter H. L. Chang, [HK] 6/4/1992, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 09.01)
    - Bu Shao-fu To Peter H. L. Chang, [HK] 11/4/1992, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 09.01)
    - C. To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 26/2/1927, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 06, Folder 06.04)
    - C. To Peter H. L. Chang, Beijing 28/2/1937, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.04)
  - Cai, Yun-sheng
    - Cai, Yun-sheng [also as Tsai Yun-sheng] To Peter H. L. Chang, Nanjing7/5/[n.y.], (1page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 04)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 45 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
  - Cao, Hui-zhen
    - Cao, Hui-zhen To Peter H. L. Chang, California 27/11/1992, (1 page, autograph letter signed; fragment of bibliography references; 7 photographs ) (Box 06, Folder 01.01)
  - Chalmers, W. S.
    - Chalmers, W. S. To Peter H. L. Chang, N. Hollywood, CA 4/8/1961, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.05)
    - Chalmers, W. S. To Peter H. L. Chang, [N. Hollywood, CA] [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.05)
    - Edith Chang To Steve?, Honolulu: April 13, 1999, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 35, Folder 03)
  - Chang, Robert
    - Robert Chang? Thank you letter for attending Opening Ceremony of H.L. and Edith Chao Chang Reading Room, New York; May 1, 2001?, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 35, Folder 04.02)
  - Ambassador Chen
    - Ambassador Chen, To H. L. Chang Berlin: March 3, 1929, 1 page -2-line autograph note (Box 37, Folder 03.05)
  - Chen, Bu-lei
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Bu-lei [also as Chen Pu-lai], [n.p.] 17/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 06)
  - Chen, Cheng
    - Chen, Cheng To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 15/11/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 07.01)
      [Note: Chang’s Personal Album, Pages 46-47 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Cheng, [n.p.] 17/2/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 07.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Cheng, [n.p.] 29/12/[n.y.], (3 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 07.03)
  - Chen, Guo-fu
    - Chen, Guo-fu [also as Chen Kuo-fu] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 19/6//[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 08.01)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 25 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Guo-fu, [n.p.] 18/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 08.02)
  - Chen, Li-fu
    - Chen, Li-fu To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.]7/7/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 09.01)
      [Note: Chang's Personal Album, page 24 [Box 1, Folder 1]]
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Li-fu, [n.p.] 6/8/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 09.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Li-fu, [n.p.] 18/5/[n.y.], (1 leaf, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 09.03)
    - Chen, Yi To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei 4/12[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 10.01(1))
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Yi, [Jingshang] 5/12/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 10.01(2))
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Yi, [Jingshang] 12/11/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 10.02)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Yi, [Jing Shang]7/5/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 10.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Chen Yi, [n.p., n.d.], (2 page autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 10.04)
  - Cheng, Guo-bao
    - Cheng, Guo-bao To Peter H. L. Chang, [Jilin Province] 1/5/1989, (3 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 07.01)
  - Chiang, W. C.
    - Chiang, W. C. To Peter H. L. Chang, Florida 31/7/1988, (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 01.02)
  - Choat, Joseph H., III
    - [Chang, Peter H. L.] To Joseph H. Choat III, Taipei 9/7/1960, (1 page, typed letter draft) (Box 06, Folder 06.05)
  - Chow, Leon H.
    - Chow, Leon H. [also as Zhou Lian-Hua, Chow Lian-hwa, Leon Chow] To Peter H. L. Chang, [Princeton NJ] 20/11/1966, (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 04, Folder 72.01)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Taipei] 1/12/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 72.01)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Peter H. L. Chang, [Taipei] [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 72.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Leon H. Chow, [n.p.] 23/12/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 72.02)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Mr.. and Mrs.. Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei 9/7 {n.y.}, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 72.02)
      [Note: with 3 page attachments]
    - Chow, Leon H. To Mr.. and Mrs.. Peter H. L. Chang, Princeton 17/3/1967, (1 autograph card signed ) (Box 04, Folder 72.03)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. and Edith Chao Chang To Leon H. Chow, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 72.04)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. and Edith Chao Chang To Leon H. Chow, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 04, Folder 72.04)
    - Herring, Ralph A. To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 28/9/1965, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Barnard, Mrs.. Everett To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 15/3/1966, (2 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Friedberg, Martha To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 9/5/1966, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Friedberg, Martha To Leon H. Chow, Tennesse7/11/1967, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Friedberg, Martha To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 11/12/1967, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Friedberg, Martha To Leon H. Chow, Tennesse7/2/1968, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Friedberg, Martha To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 8/3/1968, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Barnard, Mrs.. Everett To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 17/7/1968, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Registrar, Taipei 24/10/1968, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Friedberg, Martha To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 4/12/1968, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Martha Friedberg, Tennessee 8/1/1970, (1 page, typed letter signed(copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. Matha Friedberg, Taipei 22/9/1970, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Friedberg, Martha To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 28/9/1970, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. Martha Friedberg, [n.p.] 2/4/1971, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Friedberg, Martha To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 16/4/1971, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Hardee, J Ralph To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 24/7/1972, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Seminary Extension, Taipei 23/8/1974, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Seminary Extension, Taipei 13/9/1974, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Rigdon, Raymond M. To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 4/10/1974, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Seminary Extension, Taipei 15/11/1974, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. To Registrar, Taipei 17/9/1976, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Conn, Sue E. To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 22/5/1984, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Rose, Royce To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 25/5/1984, (1 page, typed letter signed(with a copy) and I page attachment ) (Box 04, Folder 73.01)
    - Chow, Leon H. Royce Rose, Taipei 23/9/1984, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Chow, Leon H. Sue E. Conn, Taipei 27/9/1984, (1 page, typed letter signed (copy) ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Rose, Royce To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 5/10/1984, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
    - Rose, Royce To Leon H. Chow, Tennessee 4/12/1984, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 04, Folder 73)
  - Yuan, Qingxuan
    - Chang, Peter H. L. and Edith Chang To Yuan, Qingxuan, Dalian, China: March 24, 1994, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 37, Folder 03.04)
  - Clustka, Chuck L.
    - Clustka, Chuck L. To Peter H. L. Chang, N. Hollywood,CA 8/4/1962, (1 typed card ) (Box 06, Folder 06.05)
  - Cochran, J.
    - Cochran, J. To Peter H. L. Chang, La Jolla, CA 30/11/1954, (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.06)
  - Cole, Ashley T.
    - Cole, Ashley T. To Peter H. L. Chang, New York 28/7/1964, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.07)
  - Combs, Mary Lou
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Mary Lou Combs, Taipei 3/1/1980, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
  - Committee for the Celebration of the Eightieth Anniversary of the Republic of China (Christian Group)
    - Committee for Celebration of the 80th. Anniversary of the ROC To Peter H. L. Chang, Taipei 14/8/1991, (2 page, manuscript letter signed; 1 page, manuscript letter signed; l list and 1 page printed list of activities ) (Box 06, Folder 14.01)
  - Conn, Sue E.
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Sue E. Conn, Taipei 13/11/1980, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Sue E. Conn, Taipei 14/5/1981, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Sue E. Conn, Taipei 5/4/1984, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Sue E. Conn, Taipei 2/4/1987, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Sue E. Conn, Taipei 4/8/1988, (1 page, typed letter draft (carbon) ) (Box 06, Folder 11.01)
  - Crouch, Kenneth K.
    - Crouch, Kenneth K. To Peter H. L. Chang, Bedford, VA 29/9/1966, (1 page, typed letter signed ) (Box 06, Folder 06.08)
  - Dai, Li
    - Dai, Li [also as Tai Lic] To H.L.Chang, [n.p.] 28/2 1938, (2 page manuscriptl.s with 4 page dated listings -22/1 1938 ) (Box 03, Folder 11.01(1))
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Dai Li, [n.p., n.d.][n.m.][1938], (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 11.01(2))
    - Dai, Li To H.L.Chang, [n.p.]7/1/M32 [1943], (5 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 11.03)
    - Dai, Li To H.L.Chang, [n.p.] 29/1/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 11.04)
    - Dai, Li To H.L.Chang, [n.p.] 11/6/[n.y.], (8 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 11.06)
    - Dai, Li To H.L.Chang, [n.p.] 11/11/[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 11.09)
    - Dai, Li To H.L.Chang, [n.p.] 19/8/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 11.07)
    - Dai, Li To H.L.Chang, [n.p.] 4/12/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 11.10)
    - Dai, Li To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (3 page telegram ) (Box 03, Folder 11.08(1))
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Dai Li, [n.p.] 5/10/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 11.08(2))
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Dai Li, [n.p.] 8/6/[1942, (1 autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 11.02(1))
    - Dai Li To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 21/5/1942, (2 page telegram ) (Box 03, Folder 11.02(2))
    - Dai, Li To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 5/3/[n.y.], (2 page, manuscript letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 11.05)
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To [Dai Li], [n.p., n.d.], (2 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 11.11(1))
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To ? [c/o Dai Li], [n.p., n.d.] (Box 03, Folder 11.11(2))
      [4.5 page leaf autograph letter (draft)]
  - Donald, William Henry
    - Donald, William Henry To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.]7/[n.m.]/[n.y.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 12(1))
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To William Henry Donald, Xuedou [n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter draft) (Box 03, Folder 12(2))
  - Dong, Feng-xiang
    - Dong, Feng-xiang [also as Tung Feng-hiang] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p., n.d.], (1 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 13)
  - Dong, Ping Yu
    - Dong, Ping Yu [also as Tung Ping-yu] To Peter H. L. Chang, [n.p.] 24/2/[n.y.], (2 page, autograph letter signed ) (Box 03, Folder 14)
  - Dong Xian-guang
    - Chang, Peter H. L. To Hollington Tong (Box 03, Folder 15)
      [Note; see Chiang Soong Mei-ling [Box 1, Folder 11.5]]
  - Dong, Ying-bin